https://www.lib.cam.ac.uk/privacy-policy

Email & phone search
A blend of online, zero-contact and in-person COVID-secure library services is available throughout the Christmas vacation. Find details of local adjustments, including any closure dates, on the relevant library websites.
Cambridge University Library
Home
Using the LibraryUsing the Library overview
Your library membershipYour library membership overview
Online resources and services
Zero contact servicesZero contact services overview
In-person servicesIn-person services overview
Faculty and Department Libraries
Research Collaboration
Futurelib Innovation ProgrammeFuturelib Innovation Programme overview
Inter-Library Loans
Teaching & Learning
What's OnWhat's On overview
Ghost Words exhibitionGhost Words exhibition overview
Search & findSearch & find overview
Search Library Collections
eresources & ejournalseresources & ejournals overview
Newspapers
ebooks
Janus: catalogues of Cambridge archives
Reference Management toolsReference Management tools overview
Other cataloguesOther catalogues overview
CollectionsCollections overview
Cambridge Digital Library
ExhibitionsExhibitions overview
Special CollectionsSpecial Collections overview
Collections & departmentsCollections & departments overview
Classification scheme
Recommendation for acquisitionRecommendation for acquisition overview
Cambridge Bibliographical Society
Collection Development and Management
Journals Co-ordination SchemeJournals Co-ordination Scheme overview
AboutAbout overview
GovernanceGovernance overview
History of the LibraryHistory of the Library overview
Diversifying Collections and PracticesDiversifying Collections and Practices overview
Statement on the University’s Historical Involvement with Tobias Rustat
Prizes and FellowshipsPrizes and Fellowships overview
Library Storage Facility
Press and media
GivingGiving overview
Friends of the LibraryFriends of the Library overview
Make a Donation
Philanthropy
Contact
Privacy notice
Cambridge University Library and its affiliates use your personal information:
to carry out our statutory functions supporting teaching, learning and research (e.g. providing access to or answering enquiries about our holdings)
in order to deliver our contractual obligations to you as a user of library services (e.g. responding to orders for digital images)
in accordance with the consents you have given us which you can withdraw at any time (e.g. in connection with extended borrowing rights)
to fulfil legal obligations (e.g. protecting copyright)
to improve on and keep in touch about our services (e.g. the availability of a book you requested)
in pursuit of our legitimate interests (e.g. managing the Friends of Cambridge University Library).
In connection with your registration and use of the library as a reader, we may share your data with the Colleges.
The full range of services is set out on our website http://www.lib.cam.ac.uk and our library rules are at http://www.lib.cam.ac.uk/using-library/joining-library/rules.
For more information about how we handle your personal information, and your rights under data protection legislation, please see https://www.information-compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/data-protection/general-data.
Website privacy policy
This page also explains what personal information we gather when you visit the specific website within the University of Cambridge domain called Cambridge University Library.
The information published here applies to the use of your personal information by the University of Cambridge through the viewing or use of its site.
When you visit any of the websites within the University of Cambridge domain we hold certain information about you for service and security reasons. For more information on this, please see http://www.cam.ac.uk/about-this-site/privacy-policy.
In connection with certain library services this site asks you to provide information about yourself via forms. We gather this information so that we can process reader registrations, inter-library loans, enquiries and feedback, reprography requests, philanthropic donations and membership, newsletter distribution and attendance at events and training, and to protect copyright. We use this personal data in accordance with the legal bases set out in the privacy notice above.
This page was last updated in March 2018.
Contact us
Cambridge University Library, West Road, Cambridge CB3 9DR, UK
Email: library@lib.cam.ac.ukTel: +44 (0) 1223 333000Fax: +44 (0) 1223 333160
.
Spotlight on...
About research at Cambridge
